{
    "id": "047f4e9aa219420fb2923aa98358379c",
    "title": "Always, ever, never",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9f53d3f9e72845938ad758fd382bb7ab",
            "title": "Always, Ever, Never",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Have you ..................... met my mother?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "never",
                        "ever",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will ........................ remember you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have loved him ........................ since I met him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ........................... want to see you again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "never",
                        "ever",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Nobody ....................... visits them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She will ....................... beg.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is the largest monument .................... built.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had ....................... thought of getting married before I met Gautam.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "never",
                        "ever",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Has any woman ....................... managed to climb Everest in winter?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best movie you have .................. watched?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "ever",
                        "never",
                        "always"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}